Guide to the Big Band Arrangements Collection, 1990-2017 SC.2017.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Big Band Arrangements, I.
  - My Wonderful World (Box 28, Folder 2584)
  - Nancy (Glenn Miller) (Box 7, Folder 432)
  - Nancy (Box 8, Folder 479)
  - Nearness of You, Vocal (F) (Box 13, Folder 800)
  - Never Been in Love Before (Box 7, Folder 442)
  - Never on a Sunday (Box 7, Folder 426)
  - Never Say Never Again (Marion Evans) (Box 27, Folder 2476)
  - Nevertheless, Vocal (Bb) (Box 12, Folder 757)
  - New Blues (Buddy Rich) (Box 16, Folder 1014)
  - New Kind of Love, Vocal (C) (Box 10, Folder 643)
  - New Kind of Love (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 26, Folder 2465)
  - New Places (Box 17, Folder 1087)
  - New York, New York (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - New York, New York, Vocal (Db) (Box 13, Folder 832)
  - New York, New York, Vocal (Bb) (Box 23, Folder 2242)
  - Nice and Easy (Count Basie) (Box 6, Folder 339)
  - Nice and Easy, Vocal (C) (Box 23, Folder 2238)
  - Nice and Easy, Vocal (C) (Box 24, Folder 2288)
  - Nice and Easy (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 25, Folder 2383)
  - Nice to Come Home to (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 687)
  - Nice Work, Vocal (G) (Box 19, Folder 2009)
  - Nice Work if You Can Get It (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 683)
  - Nice Work if You Can Get It (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (G) (Box 26, Folder 2416)
  - Night and Day (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (D to Eb) (Box 8, Folder 456)
  - Night and Day (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (D) (Box 8, Folder 456)
  - Night and Day (Artie Shaw) (Box 24, Folder 2295)
  - Night and Day (Marion Evans) (Box 26, Folder 2445)
  - Night in Tunisia (Les Brown) (Box 15, Folder 913)
  - Night Life (Count Basie) (Box 7, Folder 416)
  - Night Train (Buddy Morrow) (Box 22, Folder 2217)
  - Nightmare (Artie Shaw) (Box 13, Folder 803)
  - No Name Jive (Glen Gray) (Box 21, Folder 2109)
  - Nocturnal Dream (Eddy Duchin) (Box 18, Folder 1113)
  - Non Dimenticar, Vocal (G) (Box 26, Folder 2461)
  - Northwest Passage (Woody Herman) (Box 5, Folder 300)
  - Norweigan Wood (Buddy Rich) (Box 13, Folder 814)
  - Nothing but the Best (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Db) (Box 28, Folder 2551)
  - Nothing Like a Dame (Les Brown) (Box 15, Folder 912)
  - O Sole Mio (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Oh What It Seemed to Be, Vocal (Db to Eb) (Box 8, Folder 501)
  - Oh What It Seemed to Be (Harry James), Vocal (Box 14, Folder 861)
  - Oh My Papa (Glenn Miller) (Box 20, Folder 2052)
  - Ol' MacDonald Had a Farm, Vocal (E to A) (Box 28, Folder 2558)
  - Old Black Magic, Vocal (Bb) (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Old Black Magic (Les Brown) (Box 8, Folder 472)
  - Old Black Magic, Vocal (Bb) (Box 10, Folder 650)
  - Old Cape Cod, Vocal (Eb) (Box 28, Folder 2564)
  - Old Devil Moon (Stan Kenton) (Box 7, Folder 443)
  - Old Devil Moon, Vocal (Eb) (Box 23, Folder 2248)
  - Old Five Spot (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 19, Folder 1182)
  - Old Lamplighter (Sammy Kay) (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Old Man River (Bill Holman) (Box 11, Folder 717)
  - Old Wedding Ring, Vocal (Bb) (Box 26, Folder 2453)
  - On a Clear Day (Harry James) (Box 20, Folder 2060)
  - On a Clear Day, Vocal (Eb) (Box 23, Folder 2380)
  - On a Clear Day (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 28, Folder 2539)
  - On a Clear Day (Les Brown) (Box 28, Folder 2559)
  - On the Alamo (Les Brown) (Box 6, Folder 351)
  - On the Street Where You Live, Vocal (Bb) (Box 10, Folder 596)
  - On the Sunny Side of the Street (Stan Kenton) (Box 6, Folder 378)
  - Once I Had a Secret Love (Count Basie) (Box 15, Folder 921)
  - Once in a While (Stan Kenton) (Box 20, Folder 2066)
  - One, Vocal (Eb) (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - One for My Baby, Vocal (F) (Box 19, Folder 1170)
  - One Mint Julep (Count Basie), Vocal (F) (Box 19, Folder 1138)
  - One o'Clock Jump (Box 8, Folder 494)
  - One o'Clock Jump (Count Basie) (Box 4, Folder 220)
  - One on the House (Harry James) (Box 4, Folder 214)
  - One Song (Les Brown) (Box 16, Folder 991)
  - One Step Above (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Oodles of Bluedles (Count Basie) (Box 19, Folder 1169)
  - Open Up the Dog House, Vocal (F) (Box 21, Folder 2106)
  - Opus de Funk (Les Brown) (Box 5, Folder 268)
  - Opus in Pastels (Stan Kenton) (Box 9, Folder 567)
  - Opus One (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 5, Folder 258)
  - Opus One (Ray Anthony) (Box 25, Folder 2362)
  - Orange Colored Sky, Vocal (G) (Box 28, Folder 2543)
  - Our Love is Here to Stay, (C) (Box 8, Folder 445)
  - Our Love is Here to Stay (Nelson Riddle), (Bb) (Box 8, Folder 446)
  - Our Love is Here to Stay (Box 17, Folder 1064)
  - Out of Nowhere (Les Elgart) (Box 5, Folder 255)
  - Out of Nowhere (Box 6, Folder 315)
  - Over the Rainbow (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Over the Rainbow (Stan Kenton) (Box 12, Folder 759)
  - Over the Rainbow, Vocal (Bb) (Box 23, Folder 2251)
  - P. S. I Love You (The Beatles) (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - P. S. I Love You (Ted Heath) (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - P. S. I Love You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 23, Folder 2237)
  - Panama (Billy May) (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Paper Moon (Natalie Cole), Vocal (Box 20, Folder 2082)
  - Paper Moon (Natalie Cole), Vocal (Db) (Box 23, Folder 2255)
  - Paradise (Box 15, Folder 971)
  - Pastel (Harry James) (Box 6, Folder 382)
  - Patricia (Box 7, Folder 423)
  - Pavanne (Glenn Miller) (Box 12, Folder 744)
  - Peanut Vender (Stan Kenton) (Box 7, Folder 401)
  - Pennies from Heaven (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (G) (Box 4, Folder 236)
  - Pennies from Heaven (Stan Kenton) (Box 14, Folder 873)
  - Pennies from Heaven (Frank Sinatra) (Box 27, Folder 2529)
  - Pennsylvania 6-5000 (Glenn Miller) (Box 4, Folder 228)
  - People, Vocal (Bb) (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - People (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 9, Folder 527)
  - People Will Say We're in Love (Ralph Marterie) (Box 18, Folder 1104)
  - Perdido (Stan Kenton) (Box 11, Folder 678)
  - Perdido (Count Basie) (Box 19, Folder 2017)
  - Perdido (Ella Fitzgerald), Vocal (F) (Box 21, Folder 2102)
  - Perdido (Dinah Washington), Vocal (F minor) (Box 22, Folder 2186)
  - Perdido (Ray Anthony) (Box 23, Folder 2279)
  - Perfidia (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Peter Gunn (Box 18, Folder 1108)
  - Phoenix, Vocal (F) (Box 10, Folder 610)
  - Pick a Rib (Benny Goodman) (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Pick a Rib (James Moody) (Box 11, Folder 701)
  - Piel Canela (Box 14, Folder 880)
  - Pladium Party (Harry James) (Box 9, Folder 551)
  - Please Be Kind (Billy May) (Box 13, Folder 817)
  - Please Be Kind (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 22, Folder 2222)
  - Please Come Home for Christmas, Vocal (Eb) (Box 28, Folder 2566)
  - Please Don't Talk About Me (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (G to Ab) (Box 11, Folder 654)
  - Poinciana, Vocal (F) (Box 7, Folder 390)
  - Poinciana (Glenn Miller) (Box 8, Folder 458)
  - Poinciana (Benny Carter) (Box 24, Folder 2283)
  - Polka Dots and Moonbeams (Box 8, Folder 482)
  - Polka Dots and Moonbeams (Stan Kenton) (Box 19, Folder 2026)
  - Polka Medley (Box 24, Folder 2330)
  - Pompton Turnpike (Charlie Barnet) (Box 6, Folder 358)
  - Pontio (Woody Herman) (Box 14, Folder 904)
  - Poor Butterfly (Les Elgart) (Box 5, Folder 267)
  - Poor Butterfly (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 694)
  - Poor Butterfly (Box 23, Folder 2228)
  - Poor Butterfly, Vocal (F) (Box 23, Folder 2254)
  - Poor Butterfly (Ray Anthony) (Box 23, Folder 2261)
  - Poor Butterfly (Ray Anthony) (Box 23, Folder 2264)
  - Por Favor (Billy May) (Box 8, Folder 467)
  - Pork Pie (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 29, Folder 3306)
  - Pretend (Ray Anthony) (Box 20, Folder 2070)
  - Prisoner of Love (Urbie Green) (Box 13, Folder 788)
  - Prisoner of Love, Vocal (Eb) (Box 26, Folder 2442)
  - Pushin' Sand (Sammy Kay) (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Pussy Willow (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 16, Folder 994)
  - Puttin' On the Ritz (Ella Fitzgerald), Vocal (Box 20, Folder 2074)
  - Quando, Quando, Vocal (C) (Box 29, Folder 2621)
  - Quando, Quando (Box 15, Folder 975)
  - Racing With the Moon (Vaughn Monroe), Vocal (Bb) (Box 18, Folder 1150)
  - Rain (Les Brown) (Box 5, Folder 256)
  - Rainbow Around My Shoulder (Woody Herman) (Box 18, Folder 1130)
  - Rainbow Rhapsody (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Rainy Day, Vocal (Eb) (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Ramona (Les Brown) (Box 6, Folder 353)
  - Randel's Island (Ray Anthony) (Box 17, Folder 1069)
  - Ray Anthony's Boogie (Ray Anthony) (Box 4, Folder 243)
  - Recipe for Makin' Love (Harry James) (Box 20, Folder 2046)
  - Red Sails (Sammy Kay) (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Relaxin' (Count Basie) (Box 13, Folder 833)
  - Respect (Aretha Franklin), Vocal (Box 25, Folder 2369)
  - Rhapsody in Blue (Glenn Miller) (Box 9, Folder 578)
  - Rhapsody in Blue (Count Basie) (Box 15, Folder 969)
  - Rhapsody in Blue (Stan Kenton) (Box 18, Folder 1132)
  - Rise (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Riverboat Shuffle (Billy May) (Box 11, Folder 672)
  - Robin Hood (Louie Prima) (Box 29, Folder 3334)
  - Robin's Nest (Count Basie) (Box 16, Folder 1007)
  - Robert E. Lee (Woody Herman) (Box 18, Folder 1142)
  - Rock-a-bye Your Baby (Woody Herman), Vocal (Box 18, Folder 1118)
  - Rock-a-bye Your Baby (Woody Herman), Vocal (Bb) (Box 26, Folder 2436)
  - Rock-a-bye My Baby, Vocal (G) (Box 15, Folder 955)
  - Rock Mambo (Box 5, Folder 284)
  - Rocking Chair (Gene Krupa) (Box 6, Folder 375)
  - Rollin' Home (Box 17, Folder 1068)
  - Roman Guitar (Box 7, Folder 434)
  - Romance (Billy May) (Box 16, Folder 796)
  - Rose Room (Artie Shaw) (Box 28, Folder 2581)
  - Roses for a Blue Lady (Harry James) (Box 5, Folder 294)
  - Roses for a Blue Lady (Glenn Miller) (Box 10, Folder 622)
  - Round Midnight, Vocal (A minor) (Box 26, Folder 2450)
  - Round Midnight (Buddy Rich) (Box 20, Folder 2059)
  - Round Midnight, Vocal (C to C minor) (Box 26, Folder 2408)
  - Route 66, Vocal (F) (Box 20, Folder 2080)
  - Royal Blue (Stan Kenton) (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Ruby (Les Brown) (Box 8, Folder 484)
  - Running Wild (Glenn Miller) (Box 16, Folder 982)
  - 'S Wonderful (Artie Shaw) (Box 11, Folder 659)
  - Saddle Shoe Boogie (Les Elgart) (Box 12, Folder 730)
  - Saints (Box 7, Folder 438)
  - Sambita (Box 22, Folder 2176)
  - San Antonio Rose (Box 30, Folder 3338)
  - San Francisco (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - San Francisco, Vocal (Bb or C) (Box 8, Folder 454)
  - San Francisco (Count Basie) (Box 8, Folder 507)
  - San Francisco, Vocal (C) (Box 13, Folder 798)
  - San Francisco (Woody Herman) (Box 18, Folder 1131)
  - Satan Takes a Holiday (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 19, Folder 2033)
  - Satin Doll (Count Basie) (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Satin Doll (Al Cohn) (Box 15, Folder 973)
  - Satin Doll, Vocal (Eb) (Box 27, Folder 2528)
  - Satisfaction (Quincy Jones) (Box 9, Folder 514)
  - Saturday Night (Count Basie) (Box 14, Folder 890)
  - Saturday Night, Vocal (C) (Box 21, Folder 2126)
  - Say It Isn't So (Billy May) (Box 16, Folder 983)
  - Say It Isn't So (Billy May) (Box 5, Folder 302)
  - Second Time Around (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - See the Light (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 27, Folder 2484)
  - Send In the Clowns, Vocal (G-Ab) (Box 18, Folder 1154)
  - Send In the Clowns, Vocal (G) (Box 29, Folder 3333)
  - Sentimental Journey (Les Brown), Vocal (A) (Box 7, Folder 415)
  - Sentimental Over You (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - September in the Rain (Box 26, Folder 2475)
  - September Song (Ted Heath) (Box 5, Folder 254)
  - September Song (Stan Kenton) (Box 9, Folder 543)
  - September Song (Ted Heath) (Box 10, Folder 594)
  - Serenade in Blue (Box 9, Folder 530)
  - Serenade in Blue (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 28, Folder 2541)
  - Serenade in Blue (The Modernaires) (Glenn Miller), Vocal Group (Box 6, Folder 325)
  - Seventy-Six Trombones (Bill Holman) (Box 16, Folder 989)
  - Sexy Eyes, Vocal (C) (Box 17, Folder 1051)
  - Shadow of Your Smile, Vocal (F to D) (Box 22, Folder 2174)
  - Shadow of Your Smile (Box 22, Folder 2188)
  - Shake Your Booty (Box 5, Folder 273)
  - Shangri La (Woody Herman) (Box 16, Folder 1019)
  - Shangri La (Glenn Miller) (Box 12, Folder 726)
  - Shanty Town (Jonny Lang) (Box 9, Folder 549)
  - Sheik of Araby (Billy May) (Box 8, Folder 483)
  - Shiny Stockings (Billy May) (Box 18, Folder 1097)
  - Shiny Silk Stockings (Count Basie) (Box 9, Folder 589)
  - Shoo-Fly-Pie, Vocal (G) (Box 29, Folder 3328)
  - Shorty George (Count Basie) (Box 25, Folder 2351)
  - Should I (Les Elgart) (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Should I (Les Elgart) (Box 22, Folder 2187)
  - Show Me the Way to Go Home (Bert Kaempfert) (Box 7, Folder 408)
  - Show Me the Way to Go Home (Box 8, Folder 511)
  - Show Me the Way to Go Home (Ray Anthony) (Box 29, Folder 3325)
  - Shuffle Off to Buffalo, Vocal (Box 27, Folder 2474)
  - Sidewalks of Cuba (Woody Herman) (Box 5, Folder 309)
  - Sidewalks of Cuba (Stan Kenton) (Box 11, Folder 673)
  - Simpatico (Woody Herman) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Since I Fell for You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 15, Folder 965)
  - Sing (The Modernaires), Vocal Group (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Sing, Sing, Sing (part 1) (Benny Goodman) (Box 12, Folder 741)
  - Sing, Sing, Sing (part 2) (Benny Goodman) (Box 12, Folder 742)
  - Singing in the Rain (Ralph Marterie) (Box 14, Folder 876)
  - Sir Duke (Stevie Wonder) (Box 5, Folder 263)
  - Sister Sadie (Buddy Rich) (Box 5, Folder 311)
  - Sit Right Down, Vocal (Box 7, Folder 412)
  - Sittin' and Rockin' (Stan Kenton) (Box 6, Folder 344)
  - Six Flats Unfirnished (Benny Goodman) (Box 11, Folder 711)
  - Scoo Bee Doo (Woody Herman) (Box 26, Folder 2428)
  - Skylark (Glenn Miller) (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Skylark, Vocal (Db to Bb) (Box 14, Folder 884)
  - Skylark (Glenn Miller) (Box 17, Folder 1053)
  - Skyliner (Charlie Barnet) (Box 11, Folder 696)
  - Slaughter on Tenth Ave. (Box 16, Folder 993)
  - Sleepy Lagoon (Harry James) (Box 9, Folder 570)
  - Sleepy Time Down South (Box 8, Folder 481)
  - Sleepy Time Down South (Harry James) (Box 17, Folder 1040)
  - Sleigh Ride (Box 29, Folder 2610)
  - Slow Boat to China, Vocal (F) (Box 16, Folder 1005)
  - Slow Boat to China (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 28, Folder 2550)
  - Slow Frieght (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Slumber Song (Glenn Miller) (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Slumber Song (Glenn Miller) (Box 20, Folder 2071)
  - Small Hotel (Box 8, Folder 480)
  - Smoke Gets in Your Eyes (Box 23, Folder 2235)
  - Smoke Rings (Glenn Gray) (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - Smooth (Box 24, Folder 2313)
  - Snowbird, Vocal (Bb) (Box 23, Folder 2278)
  - Snowfall (Claude Thornhill) (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - So in Love (Stan Kenton) (Box 25, Folder 2355)
  - So Nice to Come Home To (Si Zentner) (Box 18, Folder 1160)
  - So Rare (Jimmy Dorsey) (Box 6, Folder 373)
  - So Rare (Les Brown) (Box 20, Folder 2037)
  - So Rare (Les Elgart) (Box 28, Folder 2577)
  - So What's New (Les Elgart) (Box 14, Folder 865)
  - Softly in a Morning Sunrise (Billy May) (Box 15, Folder 908)
  - Solitude (Stan Kenton) (Box 16, Folder 1006)
  - Solo Flight (Benny Goodman) (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - Solo for Buddy (Stan Kenton) (Box 17, Folder 1171)
  - Somebody Done Somebody Wrong (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Somebody to Watch Over Me, Vocal (Box 18, Folder 1115)
  - Somebody to Watch Over Me, Vocal (G) (Box 29, Folder 2616)
  - Something (Box 21, Folder 2165)
  - Something for Willy (Buddy Rich) (Box 17, Folder 1085)
  - Something Gotta Give (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 28, Folder 2534)
  - Sometimes I'm Happy (Benny Goodman) (Box 6, Folder 350)
  - Sometimes I'm Happy (Sarah Vaughan), Vocal (Ab) (Box 10, Folder 647)
  - Song of India (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 6, Folder 362)
  - Sonny Boy (Box 12, Folder 748)
  - Sonny Boy (Box 19, Folder 1119)
  - Sonny Boy (Woody Herman), Vocal (C) (Box 26, Folder 2426)
  - Soon (Box 13, Folder 794)
  - Soon (Box 22, Folder 2168)
  - Soon, Vocal (Bb) (Box 25, Folder 2375)
  - Sophisticated Lady (Box 17, Folder 1073)
  - Sophisticated Lady (Box 17, Folder 1090)
  - Sophisticated Lady (Box 25, Folder 2350)
  - Sophisticated Swing (Count Basie) (Box 13, Folder 822)
  - Sophisticated Swing (Glenn Miller) (Box 14, Folder 879)
  - Sophisticated Swing (Les Brown) (Box 26, Folder 2415)
  - Sorrento (Billy May) (Box 8, Folder 468)
  - Soul Kitchen (Buddy Rich) (Box 16, Folder 1032)
  - Sound of Music Medley, Sound of Music (Box 18, Folder 1107)
  - South of the Border (Count Basie) (Box 12, Folder 768)
  - South of the Border, Vocal (Db) (Box 12, Folder 774)
  - South Rampart Street (Box 25, Folder 2353)
  - South Rampart Street Blues (Billy May) (Box 12, Folder 767)
  - Southern Fried (Charlie Barnet) (Box 4, Folder 215)
  - Spanish Eyes (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Spanish Gypsy (Bob Florence) (Box 30, Folder 3343)
  - Speak Low (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 20, Folder 2039)
  - Speak Low (Bill Holman) (Box 25, Folder 2367)
  - Spinning Wheel, Vocal (G) (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Splanky (Count Basie) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Spring Can Really Hang You Up (Duke Ellington) (Box 10, Folder 626)
  - Spring is Here (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 686)
  - Spring Will Be a Little Late (Stan Kenton) (Box 16, Folder 997)
  - St. Louis Blues (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Stage Door Canteen (Glenn Miller) (Box 14, Folder 860)
  - Stairway to the Stars (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Stairway to the Stars (Urbie Green) (Box 13, Folder 791)
  - Star Eyes (Billy May) (Box 13, Folder 807)
  - Star Spangled Banner (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Star Spangled Banner (Box 14, Folder 842)
  - Starburst (Gene Krupa) (Box 19, Folder 1179)
  - Stardreams (Charlie Spivak) (Box 21, Folder 2162)
  - Stardust (Artie Shaw) (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Stardust (Glenn Miller) (Box 10, Folder 641)
  - Stardust (Bill Holman) (Box 22, Folder 2166)
  - Stardust (Ted Heath) (Box 23, Folder 2267)
  - Stars Fell on Alabama (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stars Fell on Alabama (Box 8, Folder 475)
  - Stars Fell on Alabama (Don Sebesky) (Box 25, Folder 2377)
  - Start Dancing (Box 12, Folder 773)
  - Start of Something Big (Count Basie) (Box 12, Folder 765)
  - Stealin' Apples (Benny Goodman) (Box 12, Folder 745)
  - Stealin' Apples (Les Brown) (Box 12, Folder 746)
  - Stella by Starlight (Box 15, Folder 910)
  - Stepping Out With My Baby (Box 24, Folder 2333)
  - Stolen Moments (Oliver Nelson) (Box 17, Folder 1137)
  - Stolen Moments (Oliver Nelson) (Box 25, Folder 2370)
  - Stompin' at the Savoy (Stan Kenton) (Box 8, Folder 496)
  - Stompin' at the Savoy (Stan Kenton) (Box 19, Folder 1175)
  - Stompin' at the Savoy (Benny Goodman) (Box 6, Folder 361)
  - Stoney End (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 17, Folder 1077)
  - Stormy Weather, Vocal (F to Ab) (Box 14, Folder 855)
  - Straight No Chaser (Bob Florence) (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Straighten Up and Fly Right, Vocal (F) (Box 15, Folder 966)
  - Stranger in Town (Harry James) (Box 24, Folder 2338)
  - Strangers in the Night (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Strangers in the Night (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 22, Folder 2211)
  - Strangers on the Shore (Box 29, Folder 3322)
  - Street of Dreams (Les Elgart) (Box 5, Folder 291)
  - Street of Dreams (Stan Kenton) (Box 7, Folder 439)
  - Street of Dreams (Les Brown) (Box 15, Folder 925)
  - Streets of Singapore (Glenn Miller) (Box 9, Folder 517)
  - Strictly Instrumental (Harry James) (Box 6, Folder 376)
  - String of Pearls (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - String of Pearls (Les Elgart) (Box 26, Folder 2407)
  - String of Pearls (Ray Anthony) (Box 27, Folder 2501)
  - Student Prince (Billy May) (Box 14, Folder 896)
  - Sugar Blues (Billy May) (Box 14, Folder 896)
  - Sugar Walks Down the Street (Billy May) (Box 17, Folder 1065)
  - Summer of '42 (Stan Kenton) (Box 10, Folder 648)
  - Summer of '42 (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 13, Folder 813)
  - Summertime, Vocal (F) (Box 9, Folder 563)
  - Summerwind, Vocal (Db) (Box 4, Folder 244)
  - Sun Valley Jump (Glenn Miller) (Box 6, Folder 322)
  - Sunday (Box 6, Folder 331)
  - Sunday Kind of Love (Glenn Miller), Vocal (D) (Box 22, Folder 2172)
  - Sunday P.M. (Doc Severinsen) (Box 17, Folder 1059)
  - Sunny (Si Zentner) (Box 15, Folder 907)
  - Sunny, Vocal (Bb) (Box 15, Folder 929)
  - Sunny Gets Blue (Stan Kenton) (Box 6, Folder 349)
  - Sunny Side of the Street (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 4, Folder 221)
  - Sunrise Serenade (Box 14, Folder 848)
  - Sunrise Serenade (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Sunshine of My Life, Vocal (G) (Box 10, Folder 630)
  - Swanee (Woody Herman) (Box 9, Folder 564)
  - Sway (Box 10, Folder 603)
  - Sweet and Lonely (Ralph Marterie) (Box 18, Folder 1149)
  - Sweet and Lovely (Glenn Miller) (Box 15, Folder 941)
  - Sweet and Lovely (Box 28, Folder 2565)
  - Sweet Caroline (Box 5, Folder 283)
  - Sweet Eloise (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Sweet Georgia Brown (Terry Gibbs) (Box 15, Folder 961)
  - Sweet Lorraine (Benny Goodman) (Box 29, Folder 3310)
  - Sweetest Sounds (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 685)
  - Sweetest Sounds (Les Brown) (Box 14, Folder 886)
  - Sweetheart of Sigma Chi (Glenn Miller) (Box 5, Folder 302)
  - Sweety Cakes (Count Basie) (Box 5, Folder 289)
  - Swing (Box 8, Folder 503)
  - Swing Low (Box 24, Folder 2293)
  - Swingin' on a Star (The Four Freshmen) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Swingin' Shepherd Blues (Count Basie) (Box 9, Folder 585)
  - Swingin' Down the Lane (Box 6, Folder 365)
  - Swingin' the Blues (Count Basie) (Box 16, Folder 1013)
  - Symphony Sid (Ralph Marterie) (Box 11, Folder 679)
  - Symphony Sid (Count Basie) (Box 24, Folder 2324)
  - Tag Team (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 22, Folder 2225)
  - Take My Sugar to Tea (Billy May) (Box 9, Folder 586)
  - Take the "A" Train (Stan Kenton) (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Take the "A" Train (Duke Ellington) (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - Take the "A" Train (Glenn Miller) (Box 10, Folder 627)
  - Take the "A" Train (Harry James) (Box 19, Folder 1187)
  - Takin' a Chance on Love (Si Zentner) (Box 14, Folder 900)
  - Takin' a Chance on Love (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 28, Folder 2570)
  - Talk to Me Baby (Peggy Lee), Vocal (C) (Box 23, Folder 2230)
  - Tampico (Stan Kenton), Vocal Band (Box 14, Folder 849)
  - Tangerine, Vocal (Eb) (Box 5, Folder 272)
  - Tangerine (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 27, Folder 2490)
  - Tanni (Bob Florence) (Box 17, Folder 1074)
  - Taps Miller (Count Basie) (Box 4, Folder 216)
  - Tarantella (Box 20, Folder 2050)
  - Taste of Honey (Woody Herman) (Box 16, Folder 1011)
  - T-Bones (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 15, Folder 909)
  - Tea for Two (Deane Kincaide) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Tea for Two (Les Brown) (Box 8, Folder 499)
  - Teach Me Tonight, Vocal (C) (Box 11, Folder 680)
  - Teddy the Toad (Count Basie) (Box 22, Folder 2205)
  - Temptation (Terry Gibbs) (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Temptation (Box 10, Folder 599)
  - Temptation (Artie Shaw) (Box 15, Folder 949)
  - Tender Trap (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 27, Folder 2485)
  - Tenderly (Ted Heath) (Box 11, Folder 663)
  - Tenderly (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 16, Folder 986)
  - Tenderly (Billy May) (Box 18, Folder 1098)
  - Tennessee Waltz (Patty Page), Vocal (G) (Box 23, Folder 2263)
  - Thank Heavens (Les Brown) (Box 6, Folder 355)
  - Thanks for the Memories (Box 29, Folder 3312)
  - That Old Feelin', Vocal (G or Eb) (Box 8, Folder 457)
  - That Old Gang of Mine (Les Elgart) (Box 22, Folder 2177)
  - That's All, Vocal (F) (Box 9, Folder 561)
  - That's All (Glenn Miller) (Box 10, Folder 616)
  - That's Amore, Vocal (Bb) (Box 21, Folder 2104)
  - That's Amore, Vocal (Ab) (Box 26, Folder 2441)
  - That's Life (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 11, Folder 662)
  - That's My Weakness Now (Box 15, Folder 960)
  - The Beat Goes On (Buddy Rich) (Box 13, Folder 825)
  - The Best is Yet to Come (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 19, Folder 2007)
  - The Best is Yet to Come (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 25, Folder 2360)
  - The Big Cat (Terry Gibbs) (Box 15, Folder 952)
  - The Cat (Quincy Jones) (Box 29, Folder 2609)
  - The Claw #2 (Terry Gibbs) (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - The Continental (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 4, Folder 213)
  - The Corners of My Heart, Vocal (C) (Box 29, Folder 2597)
  - The Count (Count Basie) (Box 6, Folder 338)
  - The Earl (Benny Goodman) (Box 19, Folder 1167)
  - The End of a Love Affair (Bill Holman) (Box 20, Folder 2075)
  - The Fink (Les Brown) (Box 8, Folder 500)